brandsfever.com 2019-02-10

# Privacy Policy Brandsfever

42 Venture Capital Investment Partners Limited (“ **Brandsfever** ”, or alternatively “ **we** ”, “ **our** ”, “ **ours** “, or “ **us** ”) is committed to ensuring that your personal information is protected. This Personal Data Protection Policy (“ **Policy** ”) explains how we collect, use, disclose and retain your personal information that we collect about you, and the measures that we have in place to safeguard your personal data. To this extent, we respect the confidentiality of personal data and privacy of individuals and conduct our business in line with the principles and the requirements of the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (“ **PDPA** ”). 

This Policy may apply to you even if you do not have an account with Brandsfever, and your use of our products/services means that you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy as may be updated from time to time. 

## Type of Personal Information

Under this Policy and as stipulated by law, “ **Personal Data** ” refers to any data, whether true or not, about an individual who can be identified (a) from that data; or (b) from that data and other information to which we have or are likely to have access, including data in our records as may be updated from time to time. 

Some examples of your Personal Data that we may collect are (depending on the nature of your interaction with us) your name, contact details, residential address, date of birth, identification card number/passport details or other identification number, telephone number(s) mailing address, network data and any other information which you have provided us via other forms of interaction with you. 

We also collect additional information about your interaction with Brandsfever sites and/or services without identifying you as an individual by using sophisticated Web site analytical tools and cookies in order to enhance our services and enhance your experience with us. This may include, but not limited to, device and network related information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Website, ads data, IP addresses and access/login information. 

We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual, and hence this Policy does not apply to aggregated information which summarises statistical information that would not allow any particular individual to be identified. 

## Purpose of Collection and Use of Personal Information

While you are not required to submit any information to our website, if you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to access or use some of the features and functions of our website, and we may not be able to provide you with certain services. 

This Policy applies to personal information that we may collect, use, disclose and retain in order to operate our activities and operations or to enable you to access our website and online service portals. 

For example, when you register to become a member of Brandsfever, we need to know your name and e-mail address. In the event of any transaction, we additionally need to know your billing and/or shipping address(es) and telephone number(s). Such information as well as payment-related/transactional information [credit card number, card verification value and expiry date] allows us to process your registration and/or purchase respectively. The relevant information then is used by us, our agents and/or sub-contractors to process your purchase, to answer your requests and questions. It is also used to inform you of our campaigns and to communicate with you on any matter relating to the conduct of your account or the use of the website in general. 

## We Do Not Intentionally or Knowingly Collect Personal Information from Children

We do not intentionally or knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you believe your child has provided personal information to us, please contact us so that we can identify and delete your child's personal information. 

## Use of Your Personal Information

We collect and use your personal information to operate and improve our products and deliver the services you have requested. We may use your personally identifiable information to communicate with you for all service-related issues, or to inform you other products or services available from us and our affiliates/business partners. Additionally, we may also contact you for survey related matters about our services, or to inform you of our products, services, promotions, discounts and such other marketing campaigns. 

You can let us know at any time if you no longer wish to receive marketing materials by informing us through our Personal Data Protection Officer and we will remove your details from our direct marketing database. Please note that we may still send you non-marketing messages such as surveys, customer-service notices and other service related notices. 

## Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Brandsfever will only use, disclose and/or transfer your personal data for the purposes you have been notified of and consented to or which are permitted under applicable laws and regulations. For the avoidance of doubt, where permitted under the PDPA and subject to the provisions of any applicable law, your personal data may be disclosed to our vendors or other third party service providers in connection with promotions and services offered by Brandsfever. Where Brandsfever discloses your personal data to third parties, Brandsfever will employ its best efforts to require such third parties to protect your personal data. 

Your personal information may also be disclosed by Brandsfever if it is required to do so in compliance with the law, an order of court, or the rules or regulations of any relevant regulatory or governing body with jurisdiction over the Brandsfever. In addition, we reserve the right; in our sole and absolute discretion, to cooperate fully with governmental authorities, business partners, service providers, private investigators, all rightful owner(s) or interest holder(s) in the investigation of any potential or ongoing criminal or civil wrongdoing, or if we are of the view, in our sole and absolute discretion, that it would be in our best interest to do so, i.e. mergers and acquisitions, trade sales and etc. Brandsfever shall not be liable for damages or results arising from such disclosure, and you agree not to bring action or claim against Brandsfever for such disclosure. 

For more information on the exceptions, you are encouraged to peruse the Second, Third and Fourth Schedules of the PDPA which is publicly available at [http://statutes.agc.gov.sg](https://statutes.agc.gov.sg/)

## Protection and Retention of Your Personal Information

Brandsfever has put in place various security procedures to protect your information. However, please be advised that the internet is not a secure medium. Brandsfever protects your personal information when you transact business on our website by requiring the use of a browser software program that supports industry standard SSL encryption with 128-bit key lengths. We also keep your information confidential. The internal procedures of Brandsfever cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information. 

We will also put in place reasonable security arrangements to ensure that your personal data is adequately protected and secured. Appropriate security arrangements will be taken to prevent any unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, copying, modification, leakage, loss, damage and/or alteration of your personal data. However, we cannot assume responsibility for any unauthorized use of your personal data by third parties which are wholly attributable to factors beyond our control. 

## Request for Access to Personal Data

You may request access to any of the personal information we hold about you by contacting our Personal Data Protection Officer. Please note that we are not always required to provide you with access to your personal information on request. Before we are able to provide you with any information, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help us respond to your request. 

We may, however, also refuse you access to personal information in a number of circumstances, such as where denying access is required or authorised by law, or where the request for access is regarded as frivolous or vexatious. If we deny your request for access to your personal information we will explain why. 

For a request to access personal data, we will provide you with the relevant personal data within thirty (30) days from such a request being made. Where a request cannot be complied with within the above time frame, we will inform you of the reasonably soonest time in which we will respond. 

If you would like a copy of your personal data being held by Brandsfever, please approach our Personal Data Protection Officer in person. Please bring along your identification card to fill up an application form and have your particulars verified. You will also be required to make payment of the following at the point of request: (a) If you are requesting for information on your personal data held by Brandsfever, the fees chargeable for the request is S$50.00; (b) If you are requesting for information on your personal data by Brandsfever as well as a copy of such data, the fees chargeable for the request is S$100.00. 

The above fees are indicative in nature and depending on the scope and nature of the work required to process your access request, we may be required to impose a higher fee to recover our administrative costs. This will be assessed on a case-by-case basis by our Personal Data Protection Officer. Please note that we will only process your request once you have agreed to the payment of the fee. In certain cases, we may also require a deposit from you before we process the access request. 

## Request for Correction of Personal Data

You may request that we correct any of the personal information which we hold about you by contacting our Personal Data Protection Officer. Before we are able to correct any inaccuracies, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help us respond to your request. If we refuse your request, we will tell you in writing why we have done so, as well as the mechanisms which are available to you to complain about our refusal and anything else of which we are required to inform you. If you would like to update or correct your personal data held by Brandsfever, please write to us and include the following information: (a) Your full name and NRIC No; (b) A clear photocopy of your NRIC; (c) Your contact details;(d) Name of our associate or department by whom your personal data was collected; and (e) Details of your requested correction. 

By providing to us the complete information, we will be able to update or correct your personal data as soon as possible. Our Personal Data Protection Officer will confirm the receipt of your request within three (3) working days from the date of your request. 

## Request to Withdraw Consent

It is your obligation to ensure that all Personal Data submitted to us is complete, accurate, true and correct. You have the right however, under the PDPA, to withdraw your consent to any use of your Personal Data, to obtain access or to make corrections to your Personal Data records kept with us. 

We will process your request within a reasonable time from such a request for withdrawal of consent being made, and will thereafter not collect, use and/or disclose your personal data in the manner stated in your request, as a result of which we may no longer be in a position to continue to provide membership benefits and services to you. Such a withdrawal may therefore result in the termination of any membership that you may have with us. 

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Policy or any complaints relating to your Personal Data, or you would like to obtain access and make corrections to your Personal Data records (for which we may charge a fee to cover the cost of verifying the application and locating, retrieving and copying any material requested), please contact our Data Protection Officers as follows: 

Personal Data Protection Officer  
42 Venture Capital Investment Partners Limited   
Address: PO BOX 957, Offshore Incorporation Centre, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands  
Contact No : +(65) 6570 9606   
Email Address : [pdpc@brandsfever.com](mailto:pdpc@brandsfever.com)  

## Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right, at our sole and absolute discretion, to modify or change this Policy at any time. If we make material changes to the Data Protection Policy, we will post any changes on this page. We encourage you to review this page periodically to understand our policy regarding the collection and use of your Personal Data. Please note that it is your responsibility to check this Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to our services following the posting of any changes to this Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes.
